Wow, brothers, um, come and play with you. I'm poor as hell, really. Twenty-five point eight, just tried it,
Is it in stock? It’s just this volume! Wow, wow, come on.
I, look, look, look, oops! Ah, there is no sentence for this nonsense, I made it! One more.
It turns out the link is not yours! I can't bear to fight, thank you.
This is the law of successful men, brothers! I hope you have too. If you beat him, you’ll have to beat him three more times!
I have no fucking gun!
Remember, success must be about being patient and attacking when it's most important to attack, do you understand? Listen to the picture,
I've shown my cards and listened to the picture, brother, are we really not going to curse when we fight like this? Don't worry, you said that in the future,
Let me tell you, if you kill someone like this and he adds you as a friend, just say, you learned it from Maomao.
Let me ask you, do you guys know what it means to truly not forget your roots? Although he is gone,
But I will always remember him, because without him, I wouldn't be able to eat as fat as I did. I will still choose him next time.
Choose Him steadfastly. He will definitely understand me. I will still choose him unswervingly next time.
Do you understand? OK? This is true staying true to one’s roots. I kind of want to unite, I want to touch that big red,
Mainly, mainly.
Poverty alleviation has never been a new trend for my brothers. I touched a two-by-four yesterday, and I want to touch a three-by-three.
Today I reviewed the fifteen big red dots again. Because it’s useless for you just to look at it,
You have to play it yourself, you only know, you know, right? You are very simple, let me put it bluntly,
You are doing the questions, do you know the knowledge points are useful? You have to do a question over and over again.
You have to understand that question type thoroughly and do it yourself, a dozen or twenty times.
You can never do anything wrong, right, brother? Have you really done it?
Brother, remember, when I was in junior high school, I scored one meter in math and physics, and one hundred and fifty in math.
A hundred and twenty-five in the exam; a hundred in physics, a hundred in physics or a hundred and two, a brother who takes a hundred in the exam.
The score for junior high school is 150, but not for high school.
I can only get 110 in high school math test, brother. A perfect score of 120 in junior high school is okay.
I misremembered the perfect score of 120 in junior high school, brother. It’s been too long since I’ve done this, you know, right? Damn,
Saw the black wolf.
Lan Er has done a little bit of meritorious deeds, a little bit, has done a bit of meritorious deeds. The gunshot he made in the center was terrifying.
Brother! There was no gunshot from the central control, so I stood on the central control bridge and fired randomly. After cumming on you, cum on you,
After playing two digits on the left, it is blue two.
Holy shit! Who asked you to come down? Go up! I'll jump for you!
Uh-huh! Hello, do you think that if he doesn't hit you in a fight on the hollow bridge, no one will hit you?
Let me show you the precious charm of a world-class player! Hello, skeleton activated. You mean you jumped?
Do you dare to slide the rope? I'll give you ten courages, but you won't even dare to slip. Sorry, Hai Qifeng, I admit my mistake.
This Lina just hit me, Hai Qifeng, please listen to my explanation. It's over, this life! Oops,
I almost walked away today.
Have you calmed down? You three, have you calmed down? I think you should calm down now, right?
Brother Bedou killed his sister Wang, do you know who is standing in front of you?
Standing in front of you is the God of Bacchus, the Space Executioner, the Super Warden, and the Tianba Lingzhu.